Viewers all over the world, listen.
Tell your heart, this is instruction from above.
My heart, this is instruction from above.
Right now, I press in to touch You - Jesus, deliver me!
I press in to touch You, Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua -
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Sickness is a darkness the light of God dispels.
I command light wherever sickness is located.
Light in your kidneys!
Light in your liver!
Light in your bones!
Light in your blood!
Light in your fluids!
Light!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua -
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever there is light, darkness dispels.
I command you to disappear!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua -
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Vanish in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua -
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
There shall be no trace, in the name of Jesus!
Cure!
Cure, in Jesus' name!
I love you.
Viewers all over the world, I can see you being delivered!
Right now, begin to confess your deliverance and act it.
I can see you being delivered!
Being delivered is being given dominion over satan,
dominion over evil, dominion over devil.
Confess and give thanks to God.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
To the standard of Jesus, what is not done well is not done at all.
There shall be no trace.
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua -
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
When Jesus cures, He cures perpetually!
Viewers, I know your state and I know what you are going through.
Those of us that are on the sickbed, I know what you are going through.
I know what is happening around you.
Begin to confess your healing right now.
Viewers all over the world, confess your healing.
Whatever result and whatever is coming as a report concerning your health,
Jesus is final.
Begin to confess your healing; confess it and receive it.
Confess healing and receive healing.
Confess freedom and receive freedom.
Yes.
You have declared that this is your time; this is your moment to be healed and so shall it be!
Begin to confess your freedom and receive your freedom.
Freedom in your bones, blood, kidneys, liver!
Freedom!
Somebody believes he is healed and I can hear his voice!
That is the voice of joy! That is the voice of testimony!
I rejoice with you.
I would not mind to make a crazy noise!
Hallelujah!